sup everyone TV5 here with a very
special video today you know I got some
horrified [__] news Drake Bell from
the heat TV show Drake and Josh and
critically acclaimed video game for the
Game Boy Advance has just gone missing I
don't know well yes nobody does I just
read online that he was last spotted in
Daytona Beach the police are looking for
him and there's gonna be at least eight
of us Sonic Underground fans if we all
go down to Daytona Beach right now in
Mexico then I think we can find him jack
Bell if you're seeing this we'll bring
you home we're gonna find you [__]
let's not give up on him guys I'm sure
his brother and his boyfriend
Josh pack is looking for him We're not
gonna give up on him either let's go out
we're gonna find him
we're coming Drake Bell I I don't know
where y'all but we're gonna find your
ass you can keep on running but we're
gonna find you
Drake Bell just come home
I don't give a [__] just just come
[__] home Josh Peck he's waiting for
you
that as we all are all of us the feds of
the gay boy of asking Drake and Josh we
all want you to be safe and sound so why
why do you hold me a [__]
come on uh as Sonic says from Sonic I
don't know I'm waiting